Welcome to Vocaldo, where we transform your audio into accurate text in any language.
Our AI-powered platform is designed to make transcription effortless and precise.
It's incredible how quick and accurate the transcription is,
no matter the language. Can you tell us more about how Vocaldo works?
Absolutely! Vocaldo uses state-of-the-art machine learning algorithms to analyze audio
and convert it to text. Our system can handle multiple speakers, various accents,
and even background noise with remarkable accuracy.
That's impressive! What about different file formats and languages?
Great question! Vocaldo supports a wide range of audio and video formats,
including MP3, WAV, MP4, and more. As for languages, we currently support
100 languages and dialects, making it perfect for global content creators and businesses.
Wow! That's versatile! How fast can users expect to get their transcriptions?
Speed is one of our key features. Most transcriptions are completed within minutes,
not hours. For example, a 60-minute audio file typically takes about 5 to 10 minutes to
transcribe, depending on the complexity. That's incredibly fast! What about accuracy and editing
options? Our accuracy rate is consistently above 95% for clear audio. Plus, we offer an intuitive
editor where users can easily review and refine their transcripts. You can adjust timings,
correct any misheard words, and even add speaker labels.
It sounds like Vocaldo has thought of everything. How can people get started?
It's simple. You can start using Vocaldo for free today. Just sign up on our website,
upload your first audio or video file, and experience the power of AI transcription yourself.
We offer 10 free transcriptions per month, with affordable plans for more frequent users.